Amanda Steele Show. So today's big up goes to unconditional love. This was something that again
we didn't ask for but we got it. Let's play the audio. Talk a little bit about some of the things
you've had to learn and support Serena through. I thought you were going to ask me how long it
took me to learn how to use a washcloth. So what we learned in that clip is that Serena
William's husband Alexis Ohanian who admitted to only using his hands to bathe before meeting
Serena. He may have learned a backhand. He may have learned a slice but he also learned something
important off the court which is usage of the washcloth. One thing I like about this guy is
that he really don't play about Serena. Remember he had the shirt on that said like Mrs. Williams?
Yeah. This is this is what we're talking about when we see people next to Simone Biles saying
I'm the catch. Like this is what this is what we mean. Our letdown goes to the continued school
supply shortage. So teachers are out here using their own money to provide school supplies for
their students. But some teachers in North Carolina wasted them good supplies on segregated doors.
What? A whites only entrance and a colored only entrance.
Nah. Yes. During Black History Month how about we lift up the myriad and uncountable ways that Black
people have contributed to the African-American cultural canon. The American cultural canon period.
That part.